And now I still have to run to get there.
Fell.
Yes.
You scum, what are you doing?
The woman is being beaten.
Are you
filming?
Yes, yes, I'm filming.
They ask, please, for disinformation, disinformation,
disinformation.
Misinformation.
People.
They beat him.
Well.
What shall we do?
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE.
Fuck, they're breaking glass!
I'll break the glass now, Vanya!
Stand!
Where is the police?
How can you have the right to arrest a person
without the police?
Let go, boys. Let
go, I said! Get off him!
I'll break my nails!
Call the police! Call
them, please. I'll film, you
call the police.
I'm standing behind you. Call me, run!
What are you doing,
you're there... If.
He is wanted, why
are you from the police detaining
him?
Why.
You.
Are you detaining him from the police?
On Kurchatov 20 Kurchatov 20 Closer
to school 30 Friends, is it
okay?
Fine.
Hands!
Let go, I said,
immediately!
Let go, guys!
What the fuck are you doing?
Let go!
What are you doing? Are you
breaking it?
Let go!
Let go immediately!
What are you doing?
I'll call the police now!
Let him go!
Help! Let him go!
Let go,
I said, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
Help!
No need!
Get away from them! Get away from them!
Fuck, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Get out
of here! Run away!
Run away!
Jerk!
Fuck, they saved him, and
he’s still bothering me!
The guy ran off there. Yeah,
there he is, running back.
I'm coming.
Fell.
Fuck the train.
Give me the cash register!
Move! Move!
What are your settings? You.
You probably didn't understand, did you, Pulash?
Move!
Give me the cash register!
I want to go there!
Come on, come on!
Give me your head!
Why are you hitting?